Hello, I'm curious. Here's my little paper.
If you need to relax but you don't have much time,
this is the gift for you.
Today I'm going to surprise you 30 curiosities
that you surely didn't know.
It's been five minutes.
The wings of the moon will remain intact
during the millions of years
because the moon is not wind.
The dolphins are called the ones
because it's the one cause an unknown
of each other.
A normal and direct basin
like this ruling here
can pesos two thousand kilos
with the powder and leaves that seem…
You knew...
the goats have better friends
and they make a lot of stress if they separate themselves.
One day you come to the palace
A year or less.
Do you know why?
If you know, leave me in the comments.
The combination of possible combinations in the game of the G3 is greater than the number of atoms that exist in the observable universe.
You have realized that the fire does not have shadows.
The hot water is getting faster than cold water.
It is a phenomenon known as the effect in the dark.
The crocodiles and chimneys can enter stones to get more deeply into the water.
You know that the gold is edible.
The antichrist and hypids consume in the form of salt and elegance.
The giant chino is not edible, but it is a myth.
The Romans use urine to wash the clothes.
It can be a disgusting thing, but it contains ammonia, which is a very powerful and unpleasant desegra.
The powerful is the death of the azules.
This must be in the way the light disperses through the ocean atmosphere that is full of red fire.
You know that the whales are active.
They form six months before they do.
The white butterfly has only 12 letters.
5 vowels to EO and only 7 consonants.
The red earth is called Petricor, but you already knew it.
You saw this video.
You would have to be the strongest muscle of a human body in proportion to its size.
It is the language.
In the medieval era, in addition to the second and the second, they had the moment, a unit of time that equivalent to 90 seconds.
You know that the babies have 100 bones around them, more than the adults.
The tygurons are older than the trees and the dinosaurs.
They take here from the age of 450 million years old.
The tygurons originally were purple.
You have seen that the Mona Lisa has no cemeteries or pettines.
The colibrius have the most large cerebrus inside all the birds, in proportion to their size.
They are incredibly intelligent.
The cats and the dogs, like the humans, can be furbues or disasters.
You like the smell of the earth and the short beard.
Because the reality is an exile signal from the plant.
It also serves to warn the danger to the rest of the plants.
The favorite color of most of the people, according to the studies and surveys, is the blue.
Maybe because it is associated with things as a sky or sea in calm.
You know that the national animal of the cow is the unicorn.
But it is a small country in the corner of the limelight that measures its development through the national happiness of the fruit.
It is instead a product of the fruit interior.
You know that the statue of freedom works as a lighthouse for 16 years.
Its entour was ascended and the ships that arrived at the port of New York.
The pyramids of Egypt, when they were built, were dressed in white stone.
Of the images, they would be like jewels that the plants under the sun of the desert.
What a curiosity! I have found you more incredible!
Leave me in the comments.
A special piece of paper for Angel Espazquez, Abby, Abraham Magallanes and Karen Bucanegra.
And see you in the next video.
Hello, I'm curious. Here's my little paper.
If you need to relax but you don't have much time,
this is the gift for you.
Today I'm going to surprise you 30 curiosities
that you surely didn't know.
It's been five minutes.
The wings of the moon will remain intact
during the millions of years
because the moon is not wind.
The dolphins are called the ones
because one of them is a named
full of
innate undying.
Most of the seconds have one.
A day is longer than a year is longer.
You know why?
If you know, leave me in the comments.
The combination of possible combinations in the game of the G3 is greater than the amount of atoms that exist in the observable universe.
You have realized that the fire does not have shadows.
The hot water is getting faster than cold water.
It is a phenomenon known as the effect in the dark.
The crocodiles and chimneys can enter stones to get more deeply into the water.
You know that the gold is edible.
The antichrist and geese consume in the form of salt and elegance.
The giant China is not edible from the space.
It is a myth.
The Romans used urine to wash the clothes.
You can smell the light, but it contains ammonia, which is a very powerful degreasing.
The sea poses to bring up the waves.
This must be the way the light spreads through the ocean atmosphere, which is full of red earth dust.
You know that the waves are active.
They form six months before making it.
The white leaf has only 12 letters, 5 vowels to E, and only 7 consonants.
The red leaf is called Petricor, but you already knew it.
You saw this video.
You would have to be the strongest muscle of your human body in proportion to your size.
It is the language.
In the medieval era, in addition to the minutes and seconds,
a time unit that equivalent to 90 seconds.
You know that babies have around 100 bones, more than adults.
The tygurons are older than the trees and the dinosaurs.
They take here from 450 million years ago.
The tanners originally were purple.
You look at the Mona Lisa, she has no eyebrows or eyelashes.
The necklaces have the largest brains in all the birds, in proportion to her size.
They are incredibly intelligent.
The hats and the feathers, whatever the humans can be fur or objects.
You like the smell of the earth covered with silver.
It is a sign of the oxylius of the plant.
It also serves to warn the danger to the rest of the plants.
The favorite color of most people, according to the studies and surveys, is blue.
Maybe it is associated with things as agradable as the sky or sea in calm.
You know that the national animal of the cow is the unicorn.
Butan is a small country in the cordillilla of Limolaya, who measures its development through the national happiness of the fruit.
Instead, he produced an interior fruit.
You know that the statue of freedom works as a lighthouse for 16 years.
Its entour was encended and the ships arrived at the port of New York.
The pyramids of Egypt, when they were built, were dressed in white stone.
Of the images, they would be like jewels, blood-planned, under the sun of the desert.
Curiousness has appeared more incredible.
Leave me in the comments.
A special piece of paper for Angel Espazquez, Abby, Abra Magallanes and Karen Bucaneira.
See you in the next video.